<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<document>
	<storeArea>
		<div title="Welcome" modifier="giewiki" tags="excludeLists">
			<pre>
				''Before'' you can start editing your new giewiki, you should examine,  possibly alter, and save various data for the root page. You do this via the Page properties dialog (normally part of the page setup, accessible via the edit menu on the right):&lt;br&gt;
				&lt;&lt;tabs chkPageSetup
				'PageProperties' 'Title, access, template/includes' 'js;editTiddlerHere;PageProperties;SpecialViewTemplate'
				&gt;&gt;
				The data is:
* ''Title &amp; Subtitle''&lt;br&gt;What is displayed at the top of the page and in the ~SiteMap, etc.
* ''Owner''&lt;br&gt;Who controls the properties of this page. This would be your PenName, which initially is the same as your login name, but you can change it in your [[User Profile]].
* ''Groups''&lt;br&gt;You may define a group (or multiple groups) of people that should have elevated access to the page.
* ''Access permissions''&lt;br&gt;The level of access that various user classes should have to this page.
* ''Template''&lt;br&gt;Lets you select a template (other than ''normal'') for how the page should look and behave.
* ''Tiddler libraries''&lt;br&gt;Library resources that you may include into the page.
* ''External scripts'':&lt;br&gt;For advanced applications.
* ''Page tags''&lt;br&gt;Optional. When given, these will show up in the ~SiteMap (except ''hidden'' which will prevent a page from being included in the SiteMap).
* ''Read-only options''&lt;br&gt;Various aspects of how the page looks to someone who does not have edit access:
** ''Prior versions''&lt;br&gt;Allows the reader access to prior versions of a tiddler, if they are preserved.
** ''"view" button''&lt;br&gt;Allows the reader to see the "raw" text of a tiddler, including it's markup.
* ''Fold-out index''&lt;br&gt;Controls whether the as yet empty index lists located at the bottom of the right sidebar should be presented as a fold-out element. Pages with many tiddlers would render more quickly as a result.
* ''Predefined tiddler tags''&lt;br&gt;Optional. When given, these will show up in the ''existing or predefined tags'' list when adding tiddler tags.
			</pre>
		</div>
		<div title="PenName" modifier="giewiki" tags="excludeLists">
			<pre>Your pen name shows up below the title of tiddlers that you author. If you don't set it, your login name is shown in stead.
			</pre>
		</div>
		<div title="User Profile" modifier="giewiki" tags="excludeLists">
			<pre>
				Your UserProfile is various information stored on the server under your name. It is accessed and edited via the '''my profile''' entry that is appears in the right-side menu when you click your user name. It is presented and edited using the special tiddler called UserProfile.
			</pre>
		</div>
	</storeArea>
	<shadowArea/>
</document>
